
export const data = [{
  id: 1,
  question: 'Who is the winner of the French Open tennis Women’s Singles 2022 Title?',
  choice: [{text: "Ashleigh Barty"},{text: "Iga Swiatek"},{text: "Maria Sakkari"},{text: "Naomi Osaka"}],
  answer: "Iga Swiatek"
}, {
  id: 2,
  question: 'Eoin Morgan, who announced retirement from international cricket, was from which team?',
  choice: [{text:"South Africa"},{text: "Australia"},{text: "England"},{text: "New Zealand"}],
  answer: "England"
  
}, {
  id: 3,
  question: 'Which is the host of the National Games conducted by Indian Olympic Association in 2022?',
  choice: [{text: "Goa"},{text: "Uttarakhand"},{text: "Gujarat"},{text:"Sikkim"}],
  answer: "Gujarat"
  
}, {
  id: 4,
  question: 'Which is the first country to announce equal pay for both Male and female cricketers?',
  choice: [{text:"Australia"},{text: "India"},{text: "New Zealand"},{text:"England"}],
  answer: "New Zealand"
  
}, {
  id: 5,
  question: '‘Alfiya Pathan and Gitika’, who were seen in the news, are associated with which  sports?',
  choice: [{text: "Cricket"},{text:"Boxing"},{text: "Weight-Lifting"},{text: "Fencing"}],
  answer: "Boxing"
  
},
 {
  id: 6,
  question: 'Which Indian sportsperson won the ‘Singapore Open 2022’ championship title?',
  choice: [{text: "Srikanth Kidambi"},{text: "P V Sindhu"},{text: "Saina Nehwal"},{text: "Lakshya Sen"}],
  answer: "P V Sindhu"
  
}, 
{
  id: 7,
  question: 'What is the official slogan of the 2024 Paris Olympics?',
  choice: [{text: "Games Wide Open"},{text: "Global Partnership"},{text: "Brotherly and Beautiful"},{text: "Inclusive and Impressive"}],
  answer: "Games Wide Open"
  
},
 {
  id: 8,
  question: 'Which country is the Champion of the sixth Asia Cup tournament held in 2022?',
  choice: [{text: "India"},{text: "Pakistan"},{text: "Sri Lanka"},{text: "Bangladesh"}],
  answer: "Sri Lanka"
  
},
 {
  id: 9,
  question: 'Which state is the host of the 5th edition of Khelo India Youth Games (in 2023)?',
  choice: [{text: "Madhya Pradesh"},{text: "Maharashtra"},{text: "Karnataka"},{text: "Uttarakhand"}],
  answer: "Madhya Pradesh"
  
}, {
  id: 10,
  question: 'Who has been named as the new MD and CEO of the National Stock Exchange (NSE)?',
  choice: [{text:"Ashish Chauhan"},{text: "K V Kamath"},{text: "Urjit Patel"},{text: "Arundhati Bhatacharya"}],
  answer: "Ashish Chauhan"
  
}, {
  id: 11,
  question: 'Which state Police was recently honoured with the ‘President’s colour’?',
  choice: [{text: "Tamil Nadu"},{text: "Kerala"},{text: "Odisha"},{text: "Karnataka"}],
  answer: "Tamil Nadu"
  
}, {
  id: 12,
  question: 'Which is the first Indian company to be named in the Forbes Cloud 100 List?',
  choice: [{text: "Cred"},{text: "Razorpay"},{text: "Paytm"},{text: "PayU"}],
  answer: "Razorpay"
  
}
];

export default data;
